Jose Soto

Housekeeping Supervisor

Philadelphia, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Jose-Soto/f61faefe56783455

Solid academic foundation and progressive "hands on" experience in the fields of management, hospitality, customer service, retail and sales. Ability to contribute immediately to company goals and expectations. Work well in a diverse working environment. A personable and assertive: goal oriented achiever who learns quickly, pays attention to details and combines common sense with innovation to meet and exceed goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Housekeeping Supervisor

Lollipop Condo Association - Wildwood, NJ - 2009 to 2012

Accountable for managing the task of on duty staff.

- · Confirm with the top side workplace for special visitor requests such as bouquet in room, etc.
- Oversee housekeeping staff to maintain cleanliness of individual rooms and other areas, coordinate supplies
 of linens to maintain sufficiency
- Attend to visitors calls and demand
- Report lost and found items
- · Report needed repairs to maintenance staff.

Bilingual Customer Service Representative

Lollipop Condo Association - Wildwood, NJ - 2009 to 2012

Cash handling, customer service, balance drawer and place orders for inventory.

- Maintain thorough knowledge of store merchandise and its location.
- Compile and maintain non-monetary reports and records.
- Shelf stocking and inventory.

Housekeeping

El Coronado Hotel - Wildwood, NJ - 2007 to 2009

Maintain facility in a clean and infection-free condition, Disposed of trash, waste, and other materials

- Dusted furniture, fixtures, window sills, etc.
- Cleaned basins, mirrors, commodes, tubs, and showers
- Reported any repairs needed to supervisor
- Mopped and vacuumed floors in all residents assigned daily.

Bus Person, stocker & Cashier

Borgata Hotel - Atlantic City, NJ - 2003 to 2007

Cash handling, customer service and balance drawer at end of shift.

- Food Runner
- Clean and set tables and replenish garments.
- · Stocking of coffee, sugars, sodas, milk, etc.

EDUCATION

Stetson Charter School - Philadelphia, PA 2013